{
    "id": "bb775c1fc541437884eca006ad322192",
    "title": "Sentence correction: adverbs of frequency",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9b360d9b267942c1acfb1dcc3853999e",
            "title": "Adverbs of Frequency",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He often comes very ................................. to the class.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "late",
                        "lately"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He came here two months ..................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ago",
                        "before"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He .................................... to our house.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "often comes",
                        "comes often"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Though James worked very .............................., he failed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hard",
                        "hardly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "But Peter, who took things .............................., passed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "easy",
                        "easily"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He .............................. comes to see me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "seldom",
                        "ever"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................... to meet him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "always have wanted",
                        "have always wanted",
                        "have wanted always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ................................. lazy fellow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rather",
                        "a rather",
                        "rather a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have never seen such a man he is ............................. noble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I met John last summer he told me that he had lost his father two years .....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "before",
                        "ago"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}